[{"answer": "Well, Piers, it's unbelievable and I think appalling, as you said, is a good word and also war zone, as well.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "What is it like to be actually there?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "Well, they think everyone is accounted for.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "I mean what is the state of the emergency rescue operation?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "I'll start with the first one.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "Where does this rank in terms of size and power and I suppose more pertinently what is happening tonight and which areas are most in danger?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "Yes, sir, my home was destroyed, yes.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "I know your home has just been wiped away, right?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "We're very lucky to be alive and just a good disaster plan at home and well executed at 5:00 this morning.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "Obviously devastating for you and your family but do you feel lucky to be alive?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "We were asleep -- well, we woke up half the roof was coming off the house and we managed to get the small children in the -- in the closet and about the time the small children were in the closet my wife and I noticed the walls separating from the house and it wasn't just a couple seconds later it was quiet and it was -- it was very obvious there was utter devastation around there.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "Can you tell me what it was like when you realized what was happening?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "You know, I watched it earlier on, and it didn't seem that bad on the news forecast and the weather forecast.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "ORGAN: Yes, I mean, is there anything more -- is there anything more that the people of the town could have done, do you think, or is it just one of those things when everyone is asleep and you just have to deal with what happens?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "Yes, we knew people who had been hurt today and injured in our town, yes, we did.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Mr. Hicks, did you know people who had been hurt?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "We've got insurance companies will be in here the next 48 hours and for right now a local church and a couple of other organizations put us in a motel room for the night so we're pretty fortunate tonight.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "Where will you be spending this evening, and what are your plans in the immediate near future for where you and your family will live?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "It's -- there's an apartment building about 15 feet away from it and it had picked the trailer up and thrown it against the apartment building.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "And how far had it gone?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, thank you so much for having us on this evening, first of all.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "What are your immediate actions to try and bring the town back under I guess some form of order?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "My wife called me this morning.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "How did you hear the news?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "Well, yes, we were quite good friends.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "Were you good friends?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "Oh, I think so, absolutely.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "Was he content with his life, do you think?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "It would have been just a few months ago.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "When was the last time you spoke to him, Micky?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "Always did -- did all of us, yeah.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "Did that bring Davy a lot of pleasure, the fact that you guys were back together and getting great reviews and so on?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "One of your quick little things.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "What do you want me to do?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "I really think you should have been a jockey.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely, he had family back there.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Did he remain proud of his English roots, Micky?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Oh, boy, it's a lot.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "When you're hearing all the tributes today, Micky, and all the music being played again and so on, what's your abiding memory of Davy Jones?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "Well, this is a very competitive field.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "When you think about the whole campaign so far, what do you think internally have been the issues that you've had to really confront that are the most pertinent?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "Well, there are ten states that are going to be voting on Tuesday.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "How many do you realistically think you can win on the night?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "One thing about our campaign is that we're not taking anything for granted.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Do you -- are you seeing a guy who is itching to get on to the main event?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "I would totally agree with you that we just haven't had the winter weather and that big punch of heavy snow storms that we saw last year.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "Am I right?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "Well, I will tell you, the way this goes with this -- this is, you know, 15, maybe 20 tornadoes in a cycle -- is not an incredibly bizarre pattern.", "docId": "120229pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "They don't hit directly on small towns, do they?", "qSentId": 575}]